Autumn (feat. 星尘) - AIKA/星尘
秋日私语
Autumn
风儿轻诉耳畔
Winds whisper to me
带来未曾察觉的
Bringing words I didn't know I
心之所向
Needed to hear
往事
Stories
在脑海重映
Play back in my head
珍视的时光永存心间
Precious moments we all cherish
如此珍贵
So dearly
但最终我仍无法摆脱这份痛楚
But in the end I can't rid of this pain
恍如昨日般清晰
Still feels like it was yesterday
但我记得你给予的一切
But I remember all the things you gave
你指引方向
You showed the way
回首往事 方知许多道理
Times I look back and realized many things
你赐予我的所有温柔
All the kindness that you given me
在我成长路上 你助我攀登
When I was growing and you helped me climb
请指引我前行
And be my guide
如今我踏上自己的征途
Now I move forward to pave my own way
带着你赋予的教诲与温柔
With your teachings and kindness you gave
穿越生命的阴翳
I'll keep on moving through shadows of life
寻找属于我的光
And find my light
秋日私语
Autumn
回忆温暖相拥
Thoughts hold me warmly
目之所及皆成诗
Every little thing I see
让我想起美好时光
Reminds me of good times
秋日私语
Autumn
色彩缤纷
The colors are lovely
红黄相间的糖枫
Red and yellow sugar maples
都美得令人心醉
All turn beautifully
秋日私语
Autumn
森林在歌唱
The forest is singing
这温柔的秋风如此宁静
So serene this gentle autumn breeze
在呼唤我
Calls to me
深呼吸
Breathe
慢慢来
Slowly
爱意流淌
The love flows
你的记忆给予我希望
Your memory gives me hope
我望见你
And I see you
我感受到你
And I feel you
眼前风景
And this view
让我想起你
Reminds me of you
但我会没事的
But I'll be fine
我知道你会看着我茁壮成长
I know you'll see me thrive
在那云端之上
Somewhere up high
你将见证我的闪耀
You'll see me shine
时光流逝 但痛楚仍萦绕
Time drifts on by yet this ache holds me tight
我希望我能有机会说再见
I wish I could have said goodbye
但你的回忆仍温暖我心
But all your memories still keep me warm
如此温暖
So warm inside
有时愧疚涌上心头
Some days I feel this guilt rise within me
若当初能有所不同
How things could have turned differently
至今仍能感受你的存在
Even now I feel your presence within
在我心中
Within me
如此温柔
So tenderly
Ah ha
展翅高飞吧
Go and fly away
直到重逢之日
Till another day
秋风为我们的歌谣祝福
Autumn's wind has blessed our song
歌声随晨光绵延
Our voices carry til dawn
永驻心间
Forever within our hearts